# question_data = [
#     {"text": "A slug's blood is green.", "answer": "True"},
#     {"text": "The loudest animal is the African Elephant.", "answer": "False"},
#     {"text": "Approximately one quarter of human bones are in the feet.", "answer": "True"},
#     {"text": "The total surface area of a human lungs is the size of a football pitch.", "answer": "True"},
#     {"text": "In West Virginia, USA, if you accidentally hit an animal with your car, you are free to take it home to eat.", "answer": "True"},
#     {"text": "In London, UK, if you happen to die in the House of Parliament, you are entitled to a state funeral.", "answer": "False"},
#     {"text": "It is illegal to pee in the Ocean in Portugal.", "answer": "True"},
#     {"text": "You can lead a cow down stairs but not up stairs.", "answer": "False"},
#     {"text": "Google was originally called 'Backrub'.", "answer": "True"},
#     {"text": "Buzz Aldrin's mother's maiden name was 'Moon'.", "answer": "True"},
#     {"text": "No piece of square dry paper can be folded in half more than 7 times.", "answer": "False"},
#     {"text": "A few ounces of chocolate can to kill a small dog.", "answer": "True"}
# ]

question_data = {"response_code": 0, "results": [{"category": "History",
                                                  "type": "boolean",
                                                  "difficulty": "medium",
                                                  "question": "The first televised presidential debate was between Jimmy Carter and Gerald Ford.",
                                                  "correct_answer": "False",
                                                  "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
                                                 {"category": "History", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium",
                                                  "question": "In World War II, Hawker Typhoons served in the Pacific theater.",
                                                  "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
                                                 {"category": "General Knowledge", "type": "boolean",
                                                  "difficulty": "medium",
                                                  "question": "The vapor produced by e-cigarettes is actually water.",
                                                  "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
                                                 {"category": "General Knowledge", "type": "boolean",
                                                  "difficulty": "medium", "question": "Furby was released in 1998.",
                                                  "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
                                                 {"category": "Entertainment: Video Games", "type": "boolean",
                                                  "difficulty": "medium",
                                                  "question": "In &quot;Team Fortress 2&quot;, the &quot;Bill&#039;s Hat&quot; is a reference to the game &quot;Dota 2&quot;.",
                                                  "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
                                                 {"category": "Entertainment: Television", "type": "boolean",
                                                  "difficulty": "medium",
                                                  "question": "The television show Doctor Who first aired in 1963.",
                                                  "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
                                                 {"category": "Science & Nature", "type": "boolean",
                                                  "difficulty": "easy",
                                                  "question": "An average human can go two weeks without water.",
                                                  "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
                                                 {"category": "General Knowledge", "type": "boolean",
                                                  "difficulty": "hard",
                                                  "question": "Stagecoach owned &quot;South West Trains&quot; before losing the rights to FirstGroup and MTR in March of 2017.",
                                                  "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
                                                 {"category": "Entertainment: Video Games", "type": "boolean",
                                                  "difficulty": "medium",
                                                  "question": "In the game &quot;Until Dawn&quot; Emily is the only playable character who can be killed by another playable character directly.",
                                                  "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
                                                 {"category": "Entertainment: Video Games", "type": "boolean",
                                                  "difficulty": "hard",
                                                  "question": "In The Witcher 3, the Zoltan Chivay Gwent card can be found under the Hanged Man&#039;s Tree.",
                                                  "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}]}
